[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress played the lab assistant, Inga in the movie Young Frankenstein?", "correct_answer": "Teri Garr", "incorrect_answers": ["none of these", "Madeline Kahn", "Sally Struthers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fossils of a Velociraptor attacking a Protoceratops, proving that dinosaurs attacked and ate each other, were discovered in which part of the world in 1971?", "correct_answer": "The Gobi Desert", "incorrect_answers": ["Death Valley", "The Balkans", "Bernissart, Belgium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This tasteless, colorless and odorless chemical element makes up most of the Suns volume (approx. 92%).", "correct_answer": "Hydrogen", "incorrect_answers": ["Chromium", "Magnesium", "Oxygen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of milk is used for the preparation of the Manchego cheese?", "correct_answer": "Sheeps milk", "incorrect_answers": ["Cows milk", "Goats milk", "Buffalos milk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lee Marvin played Major John Reisman in the war drama The Dirty Dozen.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For the purposes of their experiments how do physicists slow down atoms in order to study them better?", "correct_answer": "By laser cooling", "incorrect_answers": ["With liquid nitrogen", "In special refrigerators", "By bombarding them with micro particles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was the iPod touch launched?", "correct_answer": "2007", "incorrect_answers": ["2004", "2006", "2008"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1979 movie starring Faye Dunaway had this tagline:  The most poignant love-triangle of all - a father, his son, and the woman who came between them.", "correct_answer": "The Champ", "incorrect_answers": ["Rocky", "The Natural", "Easy Rider"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the essential oil made from the blossom of the bitter orange?", "correct_answer": "Neroli", "incorrect_answers": ["Lavender", "Natterdum", "Orange oilscent"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the missing word in the following dialogue from the movie Napoleon Dynamite:\nHey Napoleon, what did you do last summer again?\nI told you! I spent it with my uncle in Alaska hunting ______\u201d ?", "correct_answer": "Wolverines", "incorrect_answers": ["Mountain lions", "Grizzly bears", "Coyotes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If a computer has an integrated sound card, you will not need speakers to hear sounds (such as music or sound effects) through your system.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Leo the Lion is the mascot of what Hollywood film studio, founded in 1924?", "correct_answer": "MGM", "incorrect_answers": ["Warner Bros.", "Paramount Pictures", "Dreamworks"]}]